 ▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄  ▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄  ▄                 ▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄ 
▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌▐░▌               ▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌
 ▀▀▀▀▀█░█▀▀▀ ▐░█▀▀▀▀▀▀▀█░▌▐░▌                ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀█░▌
      ▐░▌    ▐░▌       ▐░▌▐░▌                         ▐░▌
      ▐░▌    ▐░█▄▄▄▄▄▄▄█░▌▐░▌                ▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄█░▌
      ▐░▌    ▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌▐░▌               ▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌
      ▐░▌    ▐░█▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ ▐░▌                ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀█░▌
      ▐░▌    ▐░▌          ▐░▌                         ▐░▌
 ▄▄▄▄▄█░▌    ▐░▌          ▐░█▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄       ▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄▄█░▌
▐░░░░░░░▌    ▐░▌          ▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌     ▐░░░░░░░░░░░▌
 ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀      ▀            ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀       ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ 
Release 3
Winner of the December Project of the Month on Cemetech.
Made originally for Cemetech Contest 20: Space.
By: TheLastMillennial

**Installation
Send file JPL3.8xp to your calculator.
First time doing this? Try looking at my tutorial: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gwctk-E0XXc
Trouble sending it? Look at my troubleshooting video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-TweNnHuFCQ

**Overview:
JPL is the most complex BASIC space games written in pure BASIC that is compatible with ALL TI-83/84 calculators.
Yes, finally a program that works with both monochrome and color calculators! 
In this game you get to build your ship and fly it through checkpoints and rack up the highest score.
You can also save and load your crafts for later use! (up to 40 crafts allowed!)

**Controls:
*Launch mode:
[<],[>]----------Move your craft left and right.
[clear]----------Quit

*Build mode:
[trace],[graph]--Select a part
[y=]-------------Access 'File'
[<],[>]----------Move parts around
[enter],[2nd]----Place part
[clear]----------Quit game (note: current craft will be lost)
--Shortcuts:
[S]--------------Skip immedietly to save menu
[L]--------------Skip immedietly to load menu

*Load
[^],[v]----------Change craft selection
[<],[>]----------Switch pages
[enter]----------Select and load
[clear]----------Cancel
[del]------------Delete
[y=]-------------Skip to first page
[graph]----------Skip to last page

**Save
When you click save, wait for it to load. Then name your craft with a maximum of 15 characters.
Please use only the characters: Uppercase letters (not including theta), white space, and numbers 0-9
The program will notify you if you have duplicate names.

**Load
When you click load, wait for all the names to print out. Press [clear] at any time to cancel. The screen will
show a maximum of 7 crafts per page. 
If you get a warning about corrupt lists, click 'autofix'. If things are worse off than before, you did something wrong.
Report the error at the thread linked below.

**Contact:
If you enjoyed playing, please consider voting for this on Cemetech for the 2017 Program of the Year.
Report any suggestions, bugs, or large quantaties of phosphorus at this topic: www.cemete.ch/t14186

**Change log:
V.2.04
initial release.

V.3.41
Revamped save and load system. Increased save capacity by over 12 times!
Fixed several bugs.

V.3.47
Made building *much* faster!
Fixed bug where the game would only work in Radian mode. 
Sets settings back to degree mode at the end.
Misc bug fixes

V.3.1.09
Fixes bug where you could load a nonexistant craft.
Added 7 more parts .
Added a 'skip to last page' button (and skip to first page button) for when you have lots of crafts.
Added support for scrolling through pages of crafts while it's still loading the names so you can quickly scroll to different pages.
Slightly increased the load speed of craft names.
Updated some parts of the ReadMe.